<Shows><Show><show_id>237831</show_id><network>HBO</network><title>Veep</title><time>22:30</time><day>Sunday</day><overview>A look into American politics, revolving around former Senator Selina Meyer who finds being Vice President of the United States is nothing like she expected and everything everyone ever warned her about.</overview><current_season>7</current_season><next_ep_no>1</next_ep_no><next_air_date>TBD</next_air_date><ep_title>Iowa</ep_title><ep_overview>TBD</ep_overview></Show><Show><show_id>121361</show_id><network>HBO</network><title>Game of Thrones</title><time>9:00 PM</time><day>Sunday</day><overview>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night's Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and the icy horrors beyond.</overview><current_season>7</current_season><next_ep_no>7</next_ep_no><next_air_date>2017-08-27</next_air_date><ep_title>The Dragon and the Wolf</ep_title><ep_overview>House Lannister, Stark and Targaryen meet at the Dragonpit and negotiate the future of Westeros  ...</ep_overview></Show><Show><show_id>300472</show_id><network>AMC</network><title>Preacher</title><time>10:00 PM</time><day>Sunday</day><overview>What if an angel and a demon procreate? What would that offspring be? Would it be holy or demonic or both? Preacher is that tale. The offspring has no body, just a soul. That soul needs a body and chose Jesse Custer. A preacher from Texas with a loss of faith and a drinking problem. The offspring called Genesis bonds with Jesse, giving him the word of God. What he says is done.</overview><current_season>3</current_season><next_ep_no>6</next_ep_no><next_air_date>2018-07-29</next_air_date><ep_title>Les Enfants du Sang</ep_title><ep_overview>Tulip, Jesse, Jody and T.C. hatch an ambitious plan to save both Gran'ma's and Tulip's lives; Cassidy explores a new friendship in New Orleans.</ep_overview></Show><Show><show_id>277165</show_id><network>HBO</network><title>Silicon Valley</title><time>10:00 PM</time><day>Sunday</day><overview>In the high-tech gold rush of modern Silicon Valley, the people most qualified to succeed are the least capable of handling success. A comedy partially inspired by Mike Judge's own experiences as a Silicon Valley engineer in the late 1980s.</overview><current_season>6</current_season><next_ep_no>1</next_ep_no><next_air_date>TBD</next_air_date><ep_title>TBD</ep_title><ep_overview>TBD</ep_overview></Show><Show><show_id>75805</show_id><network>FXX</network><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><time>10:00 PM</time><day>Wednesday</day><overview>Four egocentric friends who run a neighborhood Irish pub in Philadelphia try to find their way through the adult world of work and relationships. Unfortunately, their warped views and precarious judgments often lead them to trouble, creating a myriad of uncomfortable situations that usually only get worse before they get better.</overview><current_season>13</current_season><next_ep_no>1</next_ep_no><next_air_date>2018-09-05</next_air_date><ep_title>TBD</ep_title><ep_overview>TBD</ep_overview></Show></Shows>